Whether you want money or not, I will explain each of the
top 100 companies in our Indian stock market,
one by one, every day
.
How much profit and loss did those who bought those shares make in the last five years?
Are there any loans on that company? Does the
company pay
any money in the form of dividends to those who bought those shares
?  How many times has that company's shares been
split? Did they
give any bonuses?  I will explain all such details daily, such as its PE ratio, the
highest and lowest its share price reached in 52 weeks.  Let's
start with the
company we are discussing in the top 100 companies, IICI Lambad. This is an
insurance company that many people know.
While I was recording the video, its
share price was at 1772 and the
share price was changing every second
.  You can scroll up and down to watch the video
.  And its market capitalization is
88,000 crores, and its PE ratio is 32, which is
called the price to equity ratio.  The
lower this is, the cheaper the share will be
.  But
if you look at the debt to equity ratio, it's 0.01, which
means they have almost no debt.
And they are paying 0.72% in dividends every year
.  And if you
look at the 52-week high, their share
price went up to 2068 and if you
look at the lowest, it fell to 1630. If you
calculate the five-year growth CAGR, it
has given an average growth of 5%. This
share is okay for you without any difficulty.
I am collecting all the details about daily stocks and explaining it to
you in an easy way, like a banana coming to your note
.  Please give me a like and
support me.  Just looking at it and
pushing it aside like this will make me lose motivation too
.  Generally, I
provide information for two to three minutes, but
on other channels, I will show you for 15 to 20 minutes.
Okay, I don't do that to get more likes. I
provide information in an easy way. Please like and support me.
That's it. Thank you.